# **Ghifary Abrar Rabbani**

Surabaya, Indonesia | +62 856 196 2847| ghifaryabrarrr@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/ghifaryabrarrabbani/

#### **SUMMARY**

Highly organized and detail-oriented third-year undergraduate student majoring in Data Science. I have a strong passion for exploring new developments in the field. With excellent communication skills and experience in my Data Science program, I have developed a solid foundation in visualization data and analysis. Able to use languages such as Phyton and R, I have utilized these skills to gain insights from complex datasets and EDA. Additionally, I am well-versed in SQL to efficiently retrieve and manage data.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Airlangga University, Faculty of Advanced Technology and Multidiscipline

Surabaya,

2021 - Present

Major: Data Science

• Third-year undergraduate student GPA (3.60 / 4.00)

**Relevant courses:** Statistical Methods for Data Science, Data Visualization, Probability and Statistics, Data Mining and Analytics

### **EXPERIENCES**

### HIMA TEKNOLOGI SAINS DATA UNAIR

February 2023 – Now

Staff of The Department of Economy and Creativity

- Developed effective sales strategies for various products to maximize profitability

#### **BEM FTMM UNAIR**

February 2022 – December 2022

Staff of The Ministry of Empowerment of Humanity and Gender Equality

- Designing and executing project plans, which involves establishing timelines, budgets, and allocation resources
- Collecting, analyzing, and presenting data and information related to community empowerment and gender equality issues.
- Creating and distributing correspondence, such as proposal and LPJ
- Developing and implementing strategies to improve program effectiveness and efficiency

# FTMM AFTER HOUR

September – October 2022

Head of Program

- Forming a team to assist in the event planning and execution.
- Guiding participants through the screening and discussion sessions
- Selecting appropriate films or content aligned with the gender equality theme.
- Determining the schedule, venue, and event duration.

## **GENDTALK (GENDER TALK)**

17 September 2022

Secretary

- Creating and distributing correspondence, such as proposal and LPJ
- Coordinating with relevant teams to determine the theme, schedule, and objectives of the webinar.
- Developing and designing forms, such as registration forms
- Handling the webinar platform during the event, including managing screen displays, sharing slides, and controlling the event flow.

### **DEEPA FTMM UNAIR**

May 2022–June 2022

Staff of Public Relations

- Distributing letters and promotional materials to various locations in a timely and efficient manner
- Developing and designing forms, such as registration forms
- Developing marketing plans and promotional materials to increase awareness of events and activities
- Communicating with media partners to promoting the activities

- Collecting and organizing data related to competition participants

# ADDITIONAL

Technical Skills: Python, RStudio, MySQL, Microsoft Office, Tableau, Canva, Capcut

Soft Skills: Team Work, Communication, Analytical Thinking, Responsible, Time Management

Languages: Indonesian, English

License: Completion "Database MySQL: Pemula sampai Mahir" taught by Programmer Zaman Now on

Udemy